safepcrepair.com 2013-06-11

# Privacy Policy

* * *

Safe PC Repair Toolbar (“Toolbar”)is owned and operated by Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc. (Mindspark). Mindspark respects the privacy of users of our Toolbar and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. These privacy policies (the "Privacy Policy") are intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the Toolbar the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

Use of the associated Toolbar is governed by the separate End User License Agreement available 

.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using the Toolbar or transacting business with us. By using our Toolbar, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc. is a part of the IAC family of businesses (www.iac.com), which includes Ask.com, iWon.com, Girlsense.com, Vimeo.com, Match.com, College Humor, and many others. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us..

Information Collection. The general Toolbar product does not collect any personal information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.). Further, it does not: (a) collect or report back to us (or anyone else) any information about your activities on sites you visit on the Internet; (b) collect any search queries or information that you provide to any other web-sites; (c) serve pop-ups when you are on other websites; or (d) collect or report back to us (or anyone else) any data regarding your computer keystrokes or other data unrelated to the services the Toolbar provides.

Aggregated and non-personal information. We may share aggregated and non-personal information we collect. We may also share it with third parties and our IAC sister companies to develop and deliver targeted advertising. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our Toolbar and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.

Search Queries. The Toolbar, in the course of processing a given search query, sends a request to our servers. This request includes the keyword query, time of day, browser type, default language setting, IP address, an anonymous unique ID, and a code which identifies the marketing or distribution source of the toolbar used by you to conduct your search. If the search query is being generated as the result of a misspelled URL or search term entered in to the browser address bar, we also receive the misspelled URL address or search term. We use this information in order to properly process your search request. For example, this data provides us with: information on which language you prefer to use; aggregated click information for the purpose of ensuring that our search partners are appropriately compensating us; information that allows us to make accurate payments to our distributors; aggregated usage and retention information; and aggregated search query information for the purpose of further monetizing commercially oriented search keywords. All information collected from a search query is recorded on a non-personally identifiable basis and is kept strictly anonymous. The information collected is stored in a query log for up to six months. In addition, all information about search activity is evaluated only on an aggregated basis (except in response to a customer service inquiry or legal process).

Cookies. The Toolbar also uses "cookies". We do this for two reasons. First, we use the cookies to store a code designating a marketing or distribution source for the Toolbar. This information allows us to properly distinguish between Toolbar versions for purposes of analyzing retention and usage per marketing or distribution source, on an aggregated basis. Second, the Toolbar uses cookies to store user preferences. For example, we use a cookie to record which search engine you have selected as your default provider. Upon accessing the search results pages, cookies may also be placed on your computer, to store your use preferences. We do not use cookies to track your use of the Internet in any other way or to store any personally-identifiable information, and we do not disclose cookie information to third parties (other than as required by legal process). Certain third party partners/service providers may also use cookies in relation to services they provide on or via the Toolbar. For example, when you click on a third party offer presented via the Toolbar product, such third party may place an affiliate cookie on your computer to facilitate your interaction with the third party. Please note - third party sites, offers and/or cookies are not controlled by us. Such content is subject to policies of its respective third party owner (found on the third party’s website). We strongly suggest that you familiarize yourself with the policies of any third party vendor you choose to engage.

Configuration Requests/Communications with our Servers. The Toolbar sends a configuration request when you start your browser. This request is approximately 5k in size and includes only anonymous data such as IP address, browser type, and information about the specific release date and distribution source of your Toolbar, as outlined above. In addition, periodically when using the Toolbar, small communications may be sent to our servers indicating certain user preferences, as outlined above. All such information is anonymous, non-personally identifiable, and is used only for purposes of delivering search and Toolbar services and content in accordance with your preferences.

IOLO TECHNOLOGIES SOFTWARE: The Toolbar requires an additional download of certain software owned by iolo Technologies. The use of such software is governed by the End User License Agreement available at: <http://www.iolo.com/company/legal/eula/>. Important Note: iolo strongly recommends that you perform a virus and malware check of all software before installation or use and that you back up your important files and data frequently. Also – if you choose to purchase services from iolo, iolo may collect personal information from you. The collection and use of such information is governed by the iolo Privacy Policy available at: <http://www.iolo.com/company/legal/privacy/>.

OTHER PARTNER FEATURES, LINKS, RSS FEEDS: The Toolbar may include features, links to, or RSS (or other) feeds from third party partners. Mindspark is not responsible for third party features or content. If you are installing a version of the Toolbar that includes third party features and functionalities or accesses third party content, such third party features, functionalities and content are subject to such third party's terms of service and privacy policies, which may be found on the relevant partner's website.

Children’s Privacy. The Toolbar is intended for a general audience, over the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.

Using our Toolbar from outside the United States. This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on the Toolbar from residents of the United States. If you are using the Toolbar outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

No Rights of Third Parties. This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Toolbar

Changes to the Privacy Policy. We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Toolbar. We recommend that you check this page from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

How to Contact Us. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us by email or postal mail as follows:

Please contact Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc.'s Copyright Agent for Notice of claims of copyright infringement as follows:

Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc.  
One North Lexington, 9th Floor  
White Plains, NY, 10601  
ATTN: Privacy Officer/Legal Dep  
email: [privacy@mindspark.com](mailto:privacy@mindspark.com)

END OF DOCUMENT

©2013 Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc. All rights reserved.

GLOSSARY

Cookies:

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.

For example, when you sign in to an Affinity Product, we will record your user or member ID and the name on your user or member account in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, we will encrypt any usernames, passwords, and other user or member account-related data that we store in such cookies. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our website to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising.

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.

We may allow third-parties, including widget providers, IAC companies, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on one or more of our Affinity Products. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our Affinity Product websites do not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party's privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

Web Beacons:

Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.
